Guide to Local 961 Records- Harry Bath Files, 1957-2012 IBT0075
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Local 961 Records - Harry Bath Files
1957-2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0075
32 Cubic Feet Scrapbooks, plaques, artifacts, correspondence
This collection contains materials, including files and objects, collected by Harry Bath during his time as a member of Teamsters Local 961 and the Teamsters Retiree Association.
Biographical / Historical
Harry Bath was born in 1925. He was a member of Teamsters Local 961 for 41 years. He served as president of Local 961 for 27 of those years. Additionally, Bath held the position of Teamsters Joint Council 54 for 11 years, as well as many other positions on Teamster and Trucking boards. Upon retiring in 1988, Bath became a member of the Teamsters Retiree Association. Harry Bath passed away in 2012.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of materials collected by Harry Bath of IBT Local 961. The files and scrapbooks pertain to Bath's time as President of IBT Local 961. Other materials in the collection include memorabilia such as pins, a jacket, and desk decorations.
Arrangement
Series 1 is arranged chronologically. Series 2 is arranged by memorabilia type.
Conditions Governing Access
This item is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection was a gift of Harry Bath's daughter, Paula Bath. It was transferred from IBT in 2016.
General
- Harry Bath Files, 1958-2012; 1 Cubic Feet
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Harry Bath's files.
  - Rocky Mountain Teamster "Airlines Strike Seen as Fuel for Labor Haters", 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - International Teamster Magazines, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - NW Transport Services, Inc Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Harry Bath Obiturary, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hoffa/Taurone Campaign Photographs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - DRIVE Joint Council 54 Photo Album and Files, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Harry Bath Scrapbook, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Harry Bath Scrapbook, 1962-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Harry Bath Scrapbook, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Harry Bath Memorabilia, 1958-2012
  This series is arranged by memorabilia type.
  This series contains memorabilia collected by Harry Bath.
  - Julia Bath Retirement Plaque, July 31, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Harry Bath Retirement Plaque, July 31, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Harry Bath Convention Delegate Pins, 1961-1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Teamsters and Trucking Pins, 1960-1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - American Trucking Association Safe Driver Patches, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Teamsters Logo Memorabilia, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - IBT Logo Glass Desk Decoration / Paper Weight, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Derl Forbes Local 961 Teamster Bomber Jacket with Historical Note, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)